The last time we ate at a place like this
was when your sister Abi got promoted.
And now, it's you.
That's why I told you
to just trust me, Ma.
It was Benilda Cariño herself
who invited me out for dinner.
I should be the one handling this, Ma.
Let me be the judge
if you made the right choice
in investing in this shady company.
I have a reservation under Billy Cariño.
[MARIELA] Are you following my daughter?!
Cat got your tongue?
Excuse me.
How dare you?!
Let go of my mother.
- Ma.
- Karma will get you one day!
I'll be waiting.
[Rowena] I know you're doing this
because Charm is your friend.
And while I admire you
for being a good friend,
I also need to be a good mother.
- Billy. Billy, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
It's not okay, Ralph.
We're going to pull out.
This company is not good for you,
especially that girlfriend of yours!
Excuse me, ma'am.
But have you tried
getting to know Charm personally?
I hope you'll also give her a chance.
[ROWENA] This meeting
is done.
[RALPH] You don't know my mom.
She'll do anything to get her way.
But now, it's time for me
to be a better boyfriend.
I need to make a stand.
I don't care if she gets mad.
[JORDAN] See?
That's your magic.
You're like Cupid.
- That's why you're perfect for LoveList.
- Mm?
Wait. Let's take a picture.
I look a mess.
You should've taken it earlier.
Come on, let's take one.
- Okay.
- Give me your phone.
- Why my phone?
- The camera's better.
- Yay! They've made up.
- Cheers!
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- [BILLY] Oh, wait.
- Who is this?
- You're too nosy!
I've already seen it, so just tell me.
Who is it?
Someone I matched with on LoveList.
I thought you were busy.
And weren't you the one who told me
I needed a distraction?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
If I do find love,
I don't want to call it a distraction.
He should support me more than anyone
so I can stay focused on my goals.
Right? Right?
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
[SONG ENDS]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[FORK CLINKS]
DID YOU LIKE THE CAKE?
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
I ENJOYED IT.
PLEASE THANK BILLY FOR ME.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
THE BILL HAS BEEN PAID, BUT PLEASE,
DON'T MAKE ME
YOUR EMERGENCY CONTACT
BECAUSE NEXT TIME,
I WON'T BE COMING.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PAPER RUSTLING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- Billy, hi!
- Morning, Auntie Pres!
- Mmm, perfect timing.
- What's up?
Oh?
[BILLY] Mmm.
For Angels.
Are you sure?
It's all right, Auntie Pres.
LoveList is pretty stable these days,
and it's my promise to you.
Thank you, Billy.
By the way, Sir Eric wanted
to thank you for the cake.
Mmm! Welcome.
- I hope he liked it.
- What?
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- Of course.
Join me for breakfast.
I'm fine.
SORRY, I CAN'T
MAKE IT.
I'M BACK TO
WORK.
AH, OKAY… I GOT USED TO SEEING YOU
AT SCHOOL.
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- What's that, Auntie Pres?
- Huh?
- Care to share?
- [CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
It's nothing. I need to get to work.
- I'm going to be late.
- Oh, she's keeping it a secret.
I left some food in the fridge.
- Just in case you get hungry.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye now.
- Take care, Auntie Pres.
Bye! [GIGGLES]
- Bye!
- Bye-bye!
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
Hi, dude! Good morning!
Auntie Pres's birthday is coming up.
What's our plan?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, how about we celebrate at your bar?
Hello? Dude?
Let's see.
Hey, are you okay?
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
I'm fine.
I'll get going.
I've got things to do.
Okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
So grumpy.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[BIRDS CHIRPING, TRILLING IN DISTANCE]
If we hold it at the bar,
it'll be quite obvious, right?
Maybe we should do it at a resort!
What do you think?
Sounds good.
Oh, a beachside party would be fun too!
Yeah, I suppose.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[LIGHT TAP]
Uh…
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
Are you feeling ill, Jordan?
A little.
- Take the day off.
- No, no--
- Don't work today.
- I can do this.
I can handle myself.
Okay?
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Kris?
Hi! [GIGGLES]
Yes?
Oh, you're near?
Okay, I can meet you outside.
Yes. See you in a bit.
See you. Thank you. Thank you.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- Check.
- [TAPPING]
- [EXHALES]
- Coffee breath?
[BILLY HUFFING]
Smells like chocolate candy.
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS SOFTLY]
You're so grumpy!
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
- Hi, Kris!
- Hi, Billy.
Nice to finally meet you.
Likewise.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Jordan.
What are you doing there?
Nothing, uh…
I'm just taking a break.
Okay. Um…
Jordan, I want you to meet
Kristina Salintado.
She's an influencer,
and she wants to do
a special feature for LoveList.
Kris, I want you to meet Jordan,
one of our partners
and tech lead at LoveList.
- Jordan!
- Kris.
You're Kris.
Yes, Kris.
[JORDAN] Okay.
- [KRIS] Yes, nice to meet you.
- I thought…
Never mind.
Thank you so much.
- Wow!
- Yes.
- Kris.
- Kris, yes.
- She's Kris.
- Yeah.
We have a lunch meeting with Kris,
in case you want to join us
if you're not too busy.
- Yes.
- Yes?
- I'll join you.
- Okay.
Let's go, Kris.
- Come in.
[LYDIA] Remember what I told you.
Okay. Thank you.
[WOMAN] Thank you
for sharing your energy with me.
Namaste.
So, why do you look so deep in thought?
[SIGHS]
I don't know if it's right
to feel this way about Sir Eric.
Don't you feel that way about Brandon?
No, this is different.
Then what does Sir Eric have
that Brandon doesn't?
Well, he's understanding, kind,
and especially responsible
when it comes to Oliver.
But Brandon…
You wouldn't know
because you never gave him a chance.
Hey, it's not like that.
It's just that, with Sir Eric,
we've only known each other
for a few weeks,
but I already feel
so comfortable around him.
With Brandon, it's like…
I feel a little awkward.
What's that called?
Wait, is it a rebound or something?
Oh, no, it's not like that.
Besides, I never really had
feelings for Brandon.
I just got my hopes up.
But it wasn't that deep.
I guess LoveList can be wrong too, huh?
It's not LoveList's fault.
I just think you really
have to give it a try
to know for sure.
[GIGGLES]
Then try Sir Eric too.
Just tell him how you feel.
Oh, please. I don't even know
if what I'm feeling for Eric is right.
Are you a teenager? Are you?
Are you still going to play hard to get?
Oh my God. At our age,
we shouldn't waste any more time.
You might end up regretting it.
Didn't you make Rico
court you for ages before too?
Imagine if you'd said yes right away.
You could've been married to Rico
for several years
before he passed away.
Oh gosh, sorry.
- That was a bit much.
- It's okay.
- You're right, though.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
So, I can do a get-ready-with-me content
for Happily Ever After.
For the bride's side, of course.
But I was thinking,
it'll probably start in the morning
and go through the wedding,
if that's okay?
Yes. That sounds good.
But also, if I may suggest,
I think people like seeing
what's happening beforehand,
so maybe we could do
a split-screen treatment?
Like his-and-hers POVs.
What do you think?
I see where you're going.
Yeah, I love that.
- Yes?
- Yeah, let's do it.
Let's just capture the candid moments
because people like seeing
the natural side of the bride and groom.
Yeah, just let me know if we need more
cameras or POVs of other shots.
No, I think
what you proposed earlier is enough,
since you have a limited…
What do you think? Any suggestions?
- [KRIS] Yeah.
- Um…
Yep, it's good.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AWKWARD GIGGLE]
- You mean the content?
- Oh, the content?
- [BILLY] Mm-hmm.
[KRIS] Yeah.
Billy knows best.
For the content. Yeah.
Okay, I think we're all set.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Thank you so much. Go eat first.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENRICO] Olive.
Do I really have to stay away
from our children now?
I want to apologize to Billy,
but I don't want to make things
harder for her.
What should I do?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Once this is sorted out,
have the team on standby
for our next meeting.
Thank you.
[JORDAN] Dude.
You know what Auntie Pres would like?
- Hmm?
- Filipino food.
- That's her favorite.
- Correct.
It should be a Filipino restaurant.
I know the perfect place.
I'll take care of it.
- Mm-hmm.
- And there should be games too.
Mm, okay.
Those Filipino street games we used to
play when we were kids. Remember?
Auntie Pres is going to love it, I know.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
Let me see. Oh, you're not sick anymore.
You're so happy and full of energy now.
- Huh?
- Good mood today, huh?
I wonder why.
You like her, don't you?
Kris?
- Mmm.
- No.
Then why did you go downstairs earlier?
You even went to greet her.
And you keep repeating her name.
- Mm? Mm? Mm?
- Dude! It's not like that.
- You got it all wrong.
- Oh, really?
- Me?
- Yeah.
You're so happy now.
You're having a lot of fun now.
- Fine, you don't like her.
- I thought…
You don't like her because you like me.
- Huh?
- Me.
Whatever.
You don't like that?
You're too gullible.
Come on. Back to work.
Federico,
you'll always be in my heart.
You know that.
But now, someone else is
making me happy again,
just like you used to.
But I don't know.
I feel guilty.
I don't know if you're happy for me.
No matter what happens,
I'll never forget you.
I love you, Federico.
Even though I think
I'm falling in love again.
Please give me a sign
if it's right to feel this way.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir Eric.
You can tell me anything.
Is it about your family?
Does it have something to do with
your emergency the other day?
[PRECIOUS EXHALES]
If you're not ready to talk, that's fine.
Just know that I'm here for you, Sir Eric.
Just call me Eric.
Mm.
Okay. I'm here for you, Eric.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Thanks for
keeping me company.
Don't mention it.
You have done so much for Oliver.
You treat him like family.
I just want to repay your kindness.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wow!
You're up early, Ms. Supervisor.
Are you leaving already?
Well, I have to.
I have a lot of work to do as supervisor.
Ah…
Well, if your sister were here,
she'd be proud of you.
You're successful, just like her.
Hmm? Do your best, dear.
I will, like I always do.
All right, take care!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENRICO] They see her
as their real mother.
All the more reason
why you should come clean.
It'll help lighten the burden
you're carrying.
Can we meet?
I'm done second-guessing!
I'm taking the risk!
There's something
I need to confess.
I didn't expect Auntie Pres
to find love again.
Now, she has
more reasons to smile.
- ♪ Why is it like that? ♪
- [FANS CHEER]
♪ So many are rushing
To get ahead ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Why does he treat us this way?
Happy birthday to me.
Can I take you out to dinner later?
Do you know
who Auntie Pres is dating?
Hasn't she told you?
It's Sir Eric.
Your aunt is dating Sir Eric.
- Surprise!
[CHEERING]
[PRECIOUS] Billy!
You just won't leave us alone.
I only asked for one thing.
- Billy--
- [BILLY] Just leave.
Billy, what's going on?
How could you be so selfish?
You even made a fool of the person
who raised us and cared for us
when that should have been you?!